This plant wall I put up on my balcony
earlier this year — honestly, I love it.
But it wasn't mounted very securely,
so by now, about half of it has fallen down.
To make it sturdier,
this time I'm setting it up a whole different way.
I'm using a rolling rack as the frame,
and locking each pot in place with nuts,
so everything stays nice and steady.
It can even spin a full three-sixty
and roll around freely.
And the size fits the balcony just right.
You just drop the inner pot with the plant
into the outer planter, and that's it.
Right now it's looking a little too green —
it could use more variety.
So next, I'll pick up some brighter, more colorful plants
to liven the whole thing up.